http://www.hispanicfederation.org/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Hispanic Federation, Inc. is committed to respecting the privacy of its supporters, including our financial and in-kind donors, whether the donation is made online, by mail, or any other method.
Certain pages on the Hispanic Federation, Inc. site may invite you to voluntarily share personally identifying information, such as your name, address, email address, or telephone number. Sharing that information will allow you to make a donation, join our email list, sign a petition, or participate in other similar online activities. We may use that voluntarily submitted data to complete your donation, provide you with updates about the work you support, Hispanic Federation activities or news, or about opportunities to support Hispanic Federation.
When you make a financial or in-kind donation, you provide your name and contact information. Financial donors provide standard payment information including, in many circumstances, credit card data. Hispanic Federation Inc. and the companies we work with to process credit card data use industry standard safeguards to protect your information. These measures include encryption, access controls, network firewalls, and other appropriate security measures to protect your information.
We will not sell, share or trade your personally identifiable information with any other entity. In addition, we will not send mailings to our donors on behalf of other organizations. Hispanic Federation, Inc. has vendors that assist with processing and managing donations and donor data. We give these vendors access to donor data. Our vendors are bound by strict confidentiality rules and are permitted to use donor data only to support Hispanic Federation operations.
If you have comments or questions about the Hispanic Federation’s donor privacy policy, please contact Ivy Fairchild, Chief Development Officer
Go
55 Exchange Place, 5th Floor, New York, NY, 10005
1-844-432-9832
Privacy Statement
© 2020 Hispanic Federation. All rights reserved.
Design by Plus Three
Powered by ARCOS
